# **VERONICA SHEI**

### **Full Stack Software Developer**

veronicacshei@gmail.com 808.266.0688 github.com/veshei

#### Skills

### **Programming Languages**

Proficient - Javascript, Java, R Familiar - SQL, HTML5, CSS3, Python, C#, Apex

## Frameworks / Libraries

React, React Native, Angular, Spring Boot, .NET Core, Node.js,

## **Projects**

#### Locate

Proof of concept that utilized Visa Checkout data to track areas of low card utilization and conducted regression analysis in R and Tableau.

## Buy or Sell?

Predictive data science project with 81% accuracy to determine whether to buy or sell a stock. The project used ten years worth of S&P 500 data to conduct linear/logistic regression models and kNN models to build the predictions. The project was developed in R and SQL.

### College Scorecard

A website built in React and Spring Boot that lets users search for and view college data from the US Goverment and create/share college lists. Honolulu-born, Boston-trained, Austin-based.

I am a full stack software developer who is passionate about social good and crafting applications that elevate the user experience.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Visa - Software Engineer

August 2019 - Present in Austin, TX

- Lead design and development for a new value added service that will be used by issuers and business analysts as a one stop shop for the submission and management of disputes.
- Designed the external and internal portal mock ups and user flows using Sketch, InVision, and the Visa Design System.
- Developed landing page and backend apis for global dispute portal in Angular 8, .NET Core, and SQL Server Management.
- Currently driving the effort to migrate to React within Issuer Processing and working with internal React experts to craft the best base framework and CI/CD pipeline for our application.

### OppenheimerFunds - Full Stack Software Developer

July 2018 - December 2018 in New York City

- Built file drive and note editor application in iOS and Mac OS X for usage by investment, portfolio management, and research teams of a 2000+ firm.
- Developed app in React, React Native, Spring Boot, MongoDB,
   Realm, and Amazon S3 as part of a 10-person team.
- Automated end to end testing and unit testing with Detox and Jest.

# Harvard Business Publishing - Technology Consultant

July 2017 - January 2019 in Boston

- Spearheaded Slack rollout across 700-member firm by working with key stakeholders and Slack contact to ensure successful product launch.
- Managed IT projects like updating the JIRA ticketing system or upgrading video conference room capabilities.

#### **EDUCATION**

# Northeastern University

September 2015 - June 2019 in Boston, MA

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Marketing

Activities: Pan Asian American Council Cochair, Northeastern Women in Technology Member, Asian American Students in Action Mentor